Hello and welcome to our course,
Functions, Tools and Agents with LanChain.
LLMs have demonstrated
an amazing ability to
interact with humans
using natural language,
which has opened the door
to many new applications.
But how can LLMs also interact with
our existing software infrastructure?
For example, by letting
it decide when to make
a function call to a
different program to get
more information call
to a different program
to get more information
or to take an action.
LLMs were originally designed
to generate text for humans,
but some LLMs have now been
trained to output formatted data,
such as values stored as JSON,
to make it easy to let the LLM decide
when to call other code as a subroutine.
This significantly expands
what you can do with LMs,
such as let them extract
information from structured or
tabular data which LMs have
typically struggled with.
Here to tell you more
about this is Harrison Chase,
co-founder and CEO of Landchain, who has
also taught two previous short courses.
Welcome back, Harrison.
Thanks, Andrew. So great to be back.
You're right, this new capability
which OpenAI has named function
Harrison, you've described
Langchain in other courses,
but maybe you could
describe what has changed
and what you'd be covering in this course.
Absolutely.
As you know, Langchain is an open
source library that helps developers
bridge the gap between
traditional software and LLMs.
It allows developers to support
any number of different LLMs and
provides over 500 integrations
to different language models,
vector stores, and tools, as well as
supporting memory chains and agents.
There are two significant changes that
you will be getting into during the course.
The second is changes to take advantage
of the new function calling capability.
You'll learn how to use that
directly and we'll also show how
it can be used to do tasks
like tagging or extracting data.
Function Calling makes building tools
for LLMs simpler and more reliable.
You'll build some tools, and then, use
them to build a conversational agent.
You get to use all of those elements
in the course and in the final project.
That sounds great, Harrison. And I think,
Many people have worked to
make this course possible.
We're grateful to Lance Martin
and Nuno Kampas from Landchain.
And on the deeplearning.ai side,
Jeff Lodwick and Eshmel Gagari
also contributed to this course.